ACTWU's Textile Division Records 5619/038
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Complaint no.76 Local 305T. D. Nolette. Biddeford, ME., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Complaint no.45 Local #406 Election of Officers 12/2/81 (Maine Joint Board), 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Complaint Local 462 and 494T. Lewiston, Maine, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Complaint Local 462. Lewiston, ME, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Complaint no.72 Local 630 Jan Grodzki (J & J, New Brunswick), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Complaint no.51 Local 701-T. Fulton, NY, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Complaint no.53 Local 1093, Rock Hill, SC, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Complaint no.47 Local 1335, Scottsville, VA, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Complaint no.65 Local 1445 Blue Ridge Winkler. Bangor, PA., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Complaint no.66 Local 1470. Betty Crumrin, Olin Works, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Complaint no.59 Local 1495. Stearns & Foster. Beverly Barnett, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Complaint no.62 Local 1553. Helen Handow. Coatesville, PA, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Complaint no.79 Local 1604 Retirees. Canton, GA, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Complaint no.55 Local 1629. Antonio Di Salvio. Montreal, Quebec, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Complaint no.63 Local 1712. W. Warwick, R.I. Paul Fusco, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Complaint no.81 Local 1776. Geo. L. Williams, Pres., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Complaint no.71 Local 1777. Farmville, Va. (Tidewater Joint Board) #1, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Complaint no.78 Local 1777. Farmville, Va. #2, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Complaint no.61 Local 1826. London, Ontario, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Complaint no.69 Local 1836 Wilbur Kennedy, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 78)
- Complaint no.57 Local 1836, Charleston, SC, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- Complaint Local 1838 (expulsion of Pierre Asselin) Quebec, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 80)
- Complaint no.84 Local 2024 Stover, N.G. Narrows, Va., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 81)
- Complaint Local 2037, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- Complaint no.67 Local 2434, W. Carrollton, O (Steve Davis), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 83)
- Complaint no.82 Local 2247. John De Haas. Oxford, NJ, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- Election Complaint Hearing Report Local 642 Re Publication of 1981 Election Results - ACTWU Referendum, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Election Complaint Hearing Report Local 642 Re Conduct of Election (1981) - ACTWU Referendum, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Election Complaint Hearing Committee Local 642: Joseph Coponi, Chairman APPTD:, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Election Complaint Hearing Committee Local 1776. 1981 Election Joseph Coponi, Chairman, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Local 1777 - Election Appeal Ellen Emert, Prospect, VA, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Local 66T - Hearing Officer Paul Swaity - appointed 1/4/79, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Appointment of Hearing Officer Local 122 SW (C) Joseph Caponi - November 20, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Hearing Officer - Appointment and Report Local #3T Hearing November 18 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Local 3(T) Dave Balter and Brian Curran Complaint, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Complaint Local 3T, Oswego Joint Board re Donald Lamb, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Local 148-T/Bea Miranda Hearing Officer: W. Dernoncourt January 9, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Hearing Committee - - Local 224 Election Complaint (Tabone) C. Sallee, H. Officer 11/81, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Hearing Officer Alton Hodgman Local 224T - Sal Tabone. Toledo, O. March 4 GEB meeting, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Hearing - Local 250, Erwin, N.C. David Harris, Hearing Officer August 15, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Hearing Local 317-T Eden, NC. E. Chilton & M. Wilson P. Swaity, Officer, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Local 324 David Harris, Hearing officer. Newberry, S.C. Appt: June 15, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Hearing Officer Appointment Local 371, Front Royal, VA (Figgins) Hearing Officer Charles Sallee. April 15, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Hearing Officer - W. Dernoncourt Local 385 (Eden, N.C.) Bi-County Joint Board, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Local 406, Saco, Maine Hearing Officers Bruce Dunton Appointed 4/17/79 and 4/26/79. Two Cases, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Local 406, Saco, Me. Aftermath of Strike 1/79, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Appt: Hearing Officer - Murray Moreno. Greater Northern Textile Joint Board/Joseph Scalise, Local 653, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Appointment of Hearing Officer Local 687 - - appeal by Dorothy Sookram - Oct 1., 1979 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Hearing Officer - Local #944 (Wall Rope) Beverly, NK. Joseph Coponi. July 22, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Local 965 Fran Belzner v. Penn Keystone Joint Board Hearing Officer Mike Merola 4/26/79, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Local 1085 Hearing Officer: Joseph Caponi. Auburn, N.Y. Appointed October 27 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Frank Kowalsky, Local 1075. Appeal to International Convention. Auburn, New York., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Edna Manning Appeal Local 1093T. Hearing Officer: David Harris. Rock Hill, S.C., 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Hearing Officer Appointment Local #1410. T Port Jervis Murray Moreno 11/78, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Hearing Officer. W. Dernoncourt Local 1426 - Terre Haute. Ind. Aptd. April 12, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Hearing Officer - Local 1483 and Greater Fall River Joint Board. Murray Moreno Appt: Aug. 29.(Awkright Finishing Co), 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Appointment of Hearing Officer Local #1598 - Julia Brazell, Paul Swaity - Oct., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Appointment of Hearing Office Local #1598 - Helen Hriczak, Paul Swaity - Oct., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Hearing Officer: Local 1665 Darlene Geiger/ Pa Keystone JB September 11, / W. Dernon court, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Hearing Officer - Delaware Valley Joint Board v. R. Gower, Local 1710, Stockertown, PA. Hearing Officer - Bruce Dunton Appointed October 28., 1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Local 1782 - Hearing Comm charges against Don Warner Appointed Jan 29, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Hearing Officer - Local 1874(T) Appointed May 30, Wayne Dernoncourt, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Hearing Officer Local 1888 Sagertown. Pa. George Dillman, Appointed 2/17/77, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Appointment of Hearing Officer Pacific Northwest Joint Board William Himes, Herring Officer November 7 (charges against Manager Frank (Red) Beyers), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Convention - Appeals from GEB Decisions Pacific Northwest Joint Board, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Appointment of Hearing Officer:, Robert Pacheco, Greater Fall River Joint Board August 15, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Greater Fall River Joint Board Hearing Officer W. Dernoncourt Appointed Dec. 27, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Fall River Joint Board Hearing Officer W. Dernoncourt. Jan 24, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Greater Fall River Joint Board - Hearing Officer: Bruce Dunton - Report 11/78 - Related Matters, 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Hearing Officer - Wayne Dernoncourt Greater Fall River Joint Board, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- JPS - Clyde Bush Special Reports, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- JPS Company Supporters, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- JPS - Company Film - The Issue - The Right to Choose, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- JPS Company's Statements (various), 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- JPS - Company supporters Stevens Employees Educational Committee #2, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- JPS Corporate Campaign, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- JPS Company's Letters to its workers, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- JPS Roanoke Rapids Contract Data Oct., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- JPS Human Rights Report. Si Kahn, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- JPS History of Organizing (4x Draft, also History Non-Textile Plants), 1975-1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- JPS The Willie Brice "story", 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- JPS IUD Harold McIver Campaign Coordinator - Misc. Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- JPS Magazine Articles, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- JPS History of Campaign up to 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- JPS High Point, NC plant Election 10-4-79, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- JPS Stevens Boycott, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- JPS Company Ads, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- JP Stevens - New Guide for Employees - Jan, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- JPS - Articles, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- JPS - ACTWU News Press Releases, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- JPS Boycott Strategy, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- JPS - Civil Rights Problems, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- JPS - The Church and J.P. Stevens, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- JPS - Boycott, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- JPS: Heritage Foundation Report, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- JPS Finley, James D., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- JPS Financial Status (Co.-Defense Contracts), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- JPS Foreign Operations, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- JPS Government Contracts, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- JPS Jessie Hawkins Rally & Demonstration 9-14-78, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- JPS - EEOC re: Organizers, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- JPS Expenses (non-IUD), 1974-1980 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- JPS Governor Byrne, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- JPS IUD Expenses Paid by ACTWU, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- JPS Fabric of Injustice (The Struggle of JPS) booklet, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- JPS Financial Condition of JPS of ACTWU Boycott, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- JPS Corduroy Plant, Greenville, SC, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- JP Stevens - Boycott CUPS, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- JPS DEED (with discriminatory clause), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- JPS East Hampton, Mass. Plant, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- JPS Bulletin Boards (correspondence), 1969-1979 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- JPS: Political contributions from J.P. Stevens, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- JPS Connecticut State Bill & Misc, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- JPS Contract Comparisons, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- JPS Contributions to Campaign, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- JPS Allendale Plant Election petition, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- JPS Annual Reports Financial Statements, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Louise Bailey Reference to her in AFL-CIO Convention., 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- JPS Union Charters, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- JPS Citizens Committee for Justice for J.P. Stevens Workers., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- JPS Transfile no.142, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- JPS Jorgensen, Keir Reports on JPS contracts, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- JPS Crystal Lee Jordon Gail Jeffords -- Public Relations, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- JPS Crystal Lee Jordan Sutton Unemployment Case, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- JPS Crystal Lee Jordon, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Prime Time - Crystal Lee Jordan, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Kopple, Barbara, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Congressional Reception for Crystal Lee Sutton June 11, 5:30 PM Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Crystal Lee Jordon - Roanoke Rapids, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- JPS Gail Jeffords - Reports, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- JPS Leadership Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- JPS Labor Law Reform (as applied to JPS, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens "Social Justice", 1976-1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens - Wallace Decision, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Institute for Southern Studies, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- JPS Kit for Media, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- JPS International Labor Support, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- JPS Japanese Boycott. Support for JPS Workers, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens. Si Kahn Services, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- File on Wallace -, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- JPS Legal Wallace, N.C. Case & Decision, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Cannon Mills Kannapolis, N.C., 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Cannon Mills Clippings, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Cannon Mills, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Cannon Mills, 1980-1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Cannon Newspaper Clippings, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Canon (Hoyman), 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Cannonball Express, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Cannon Staff Meeting Tuesday March 10, NYC 10:30 AM, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Cannon Mills staff Meeting Friday, August 8, NYC, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Cone Locals, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Cone Mills Negotiations for Agreement for Transfer of Employees with impaired pulmonary function, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Cone Mills Negotiations, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Cone Mills - Arbitration of Discharge of Rand Manzella (CWP) May, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Cone Council, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Cone Union Council, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Cone Project Materials, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- July Cone Materials, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Cone Bills - approved by Scott Hoyman (October-December), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Cone Revolving Fund, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Cone Union Council Revolving Fund, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Cone Union Council, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Cone Workers' Union Voice, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Cone Workers' Union Voice, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Darlington, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Darlington Workers, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Deering Milliken - Darlington. S.C. Communications on situation., 1972-1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Fieldcrest - Coordinated Bargaining, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Fieldcrest - Misc., 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Fieldcrest Mills Scottsboro, Ala., 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Fieldcrest - Francis Larkin President, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Comparison of Fieldcrest contract w/Erwin, Cone and Stevens Memo by J. Weiser 12/19/80 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Fieldcrest - Membership Drive September, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- All Fieldcrest Eden, N.C., 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Fieldcrest - Clippings, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Fieldcrest Visit. Tour with M. Finley/S. Hoyman etc. October 7, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- United Merchants & Manufacturers, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Uniglass United Merchants Statesville, N.C., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- United Merchants Memorandum of Agreement Atlanta, Ga., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- United Merchants and Manufacturing 1407 Broadway NYC, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- United Merchants Homestead Plant Augusta, Georgia, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- United Merchants and Manufacturers, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- United Merchants/Machine Printers and Engraves, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  Scope and Contents
  Monday, June 29, 1981
- Transfile no.143 J.P. Stevens & Co., 1980 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal Matters, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens & Co. Williams & Thompson Correspondence on Cases 11-CA-7865 11-CA-8057, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens Legal Easthampton, Mass. NLRB case Rubber Workers, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens Legal Folder no.3, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Brief to Administrative Law Judge J.P. Stevens Tifton, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- McConville, Ed. "Story of J.P. Stevens" Outline & Chapters, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens & Company NLRB Cases, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Los Angeles Hearings, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott, 1979-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- McConville The Nation Article, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Norma Rae Show- Capitol Hill, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Norma Rae Atlanta Constitution article on Crystal Lee, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Norma Rae screening by AFSCME and IATSE, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Norma Rae Charlotte Observer, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  3-11-1979
- Norma Rae Martin Ritt, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Nation's Labor, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens & Company New England Region paper Boycott News, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Del Mileski, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Mileski Reports (1 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Mileski Reports (2 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Ed McConville, 1977-1981 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal Matters, 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Legal Folder #4, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens National Alliance Against Racial & Political Oppression, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens & Company National Citizens Committee, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Byrne, Brendan, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens & Company New Zealand Contracts, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Norma Rae Film, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Norma Rae Misc. Clippings/ Reviews, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Norma Rae General Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Organizing Reports & Activities, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Organizing Staff, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Meeting with Bishop of Paterson re. J.P. Stevens, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Personal Testimonies, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Pittsburgh Area Activity, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Plant Purchases, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Products, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Press Conference & Rally, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Publicity, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Boycott Rally Knoxville, TN, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Stevens Rally/ Joint Board Meeting Knoxville/ St. Louis, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Rally Rome, Ga., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Birmingham Rally, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- J.P. Stevens High School Rally Edison, NJ, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- J.P. Stevens Protest Meetings, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Interchurch Federation Indianapolis, Ind., 1979 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Rally Macon, Ga., 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- J.P. Stevens Public Relations Michael Klepper Associates, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- J.P. Stevens Mile Long Human Billboard for Justice, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott Supporters Indianapolis, Ind., 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens Organizing Campaign, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- J.P. Stevens 5th Anniversary Rally Roanoke Rapids, N.C., 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- J.P. Stevens Visit to Roanoke Rapids, N.C., 1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Meet Crystal Lee Sutton Rally L.A. California, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Justice for J.P. Stevens Workers Day Nation-wide, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- J.P. Stevens Action at Gimbels, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  January
- J.P. Stevens Rally Boston, Mass., 1978 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- J.P. Stevens Rally Quebec, Canada, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- J.P. Stevens Breakfast Meeting W. Orange, NJ, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Dayton-Miami Valley Labor Council Stevens Rally Dayton, Ohio, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Atlanta Press Conference & ride to Rome, Ga., 1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens Rallies (Misc.), 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens "The Record" article by Mike Hoyt, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens Recidivist, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- J.P. Stevens Response to Statement from ACTWU, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- J.P. Stevens Roanoke Rapids Proposed Contract, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- J.P. Stevens Boycott, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- J.P. Stevens, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- J.P. Stevens, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- J.P. Stevens, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- J.P. Stevens Staff, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- J.P. Stevens Negotiations, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- J.P. Stevens Roanoke Rapids Bargaining Unit, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- J.P. Stevens & Company Report of Activities from Paul Swaity, 1974-1978 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Delinquent Per Capita Cash Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- ACTWU Amalgamated Action, 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- ACTWU Dues Increases (Local and Joint Board), 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Dues Rates Above Minimum Requirements GEB Textile Mailing, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- ACTWU Dues Payments Requests for Waiver of Dues Increase, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Johnson-Johnson, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- ACTWU General Executive Board Communications from Officers, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- ACTWU International Trade Affairs Art Gundersheim, Director, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- C Lazzio, J Novak, A Gundershiem re: Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- ACTWU Legal, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Legal Pending Legal Matters, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Merger Pamphlet, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Legislative and Political Education Department, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- ACTWU Logos, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- ACTWU McBride Team, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Publicity, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- ACTWU Samuel, Howard, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- ACTWU Jack Sheinkman Secretary Treasurer, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Memorial Services for Val Wertheimer, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Textile Division Inactive Administrative Assistants, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Charles Sallee Bag Industry Director, 1966-1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Bag & Packaging Conference St. Louis, Mo., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Bag Conference, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Annual Bag and Packaging Conference St. Louis, Mo. Roadway Inn, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- New England Plymouth Cordage, 1966-1972 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Rope and Cordage Conference, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Rope and Cordage Locals, 1964-1977 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Cordage Industry Position H.R. 5629 Trade Sub-Committee, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Dyers Industry, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Dyers Strike Press Releases and Clippings, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- ATP Processors Contract Negotiations, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Dyeing & Fin Organizing Campaign, 1975-1978 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Dyers Division Allied Textile Printers, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Dyers Division Mtg. Providence, RI Leadership Meeting, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Dyers Division Meeting Lyndhurst, N.J., 1977 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Circulation Dept., 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Circulation Dept. Labor Unity Delinquency List, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Circulation Dept. 1977 Annual Report, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Weber, George Report of Circulation Dept., 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Education Dept. Textile Division, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- ACTWU Engineering Dept., 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- ACTWU Engineering Dept., 1977 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Finance Dept., 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Organizing (Textile Division), 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Engineering Dept., 1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Organizing (Textile Division), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Research, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Organizing Dept. Evaluation of Elections, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Publicity Labor Unity Tom Herriman, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Publicity, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Survey Research Methods, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Everett Kassalow's Ideas University of Wisconsin, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Safety and Health Manual (Local Union), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- OSHA Temporary Folder, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Academic Press, Inc. & Johnson Reprint Corp. Strike Local 1870 Palisades, NY, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Ackerman Mfg. Co. Local 1594-T St. Louis, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Acme-Chaston Local 1196T Dayville, Conn., 1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Affiliated Medical Products Ltd. Local 1775, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Ajusto Equipment Co. Local 1758 Bowling Green, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Allen Industries DAYCO Compton, Calif. Local 1373, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Alton Box Board Local 2423 Cedartown, Ga., 1979-1982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- American Wholesalers Strike Local 2331 Landsover, Md., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Aries Corp Strike Local 2052 Union City, NJ, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Berkshire Hathaway Strike Local 590T New Bedford, Mass., 1980 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Best Manufacturing Strike B. Baynor's area, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 22)